thetoptens.com 2013-12-11

# TheTopTens - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting TheTopTens. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

## Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. 

## Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site makes use cookies and other tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be gathered via cookies and other tracking technology. Cookie and tracking information will not be shared with third parties. 

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

## Distribution of Information

We will only share collected information with third parties when we are legally required to do so. Information will never be provided to third parties for marketing purposes. 

**Featured Lists**

**Popular Lists**

**New Lists**
